你刚刚完成的重构得到我们的代码
The refactoring you just
completed gets our code
准备使用weather provider
ready to use the weather provider.
对这次测试 你将编写addLocation方法
For this quiz, you're going to
code the addLocation method.
如你所见 这个方法拿到一个locationSetting,cityName
As you can see, this method takes
a locationSetting, cityName,
纬度和经度为新的位置
latitude and longitude for
the new location.
如果这个位置已经存在 我们返回这个存在的位置的ID
If the location already exists, we
return the ID of the existing location.
如果我们添加一个新的位置，我们返回那个添加的位置的ID
If we add a location,
we return the ID of the added location.
我们第一步先查询这个content provider
We can do this by first
querying the content provider,
来看看查询的位置是否存在
to see if the location
query already exists, and
仅仅位置不存在的时候进行插入操作
only performing the insert
if it doesn't yet exist.
取消在测试抓取天气的任务中测试添加位置的代码
Uncomment test add location
within test fetch weather task,
来验证你的答案
to validate your solution.